{
    "subject": "resource/Fernando_Pessoa",
    "predicate": "ontology/influenced",
    "object": "resource/Antonio_Tabucchi",
    "human_readable": "Fernando Pessoa was influenced by Antonio Tabucchi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9863162636756897,
            "question": "Was Antonio Tabucchi a source of inspiration for Fernando Pessoa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9181990623474121,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Fernando Pessoa and Antonio Tabucchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9145568609237671,
            "question": "What connection existed between Fernando Pessoa and Antonio Tabucchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8986071348190308,
            "question": "Who influenced Fernando Pessoa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.729354739189148,
            "question": "Who was a literary influence on Fernando Pessoa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6700684428215027,
            "question": "Name a writer who influenced Fernando Pessoa."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6378771066665649,
            "question": "Which prominent author inspired Fernando Pessoa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6213493943214417,
            "question": "Fernando Pessoa acknowledged the influence of which writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47990554571151733,
            "question": "Can you identify any writers who had an impact on Fernando Pessoa's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18801432847976685,
            "question": "What writers might have shaped Fernando Pessoa's writing style?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fernando Pessoa was influenced by Antonio Tabucchi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8486_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify any writers who had an impact on Fernando Pessoa's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8486_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fernando Pessoa acknowledged the influence of which writer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8486_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which prominent author inspired Fernando Pessoa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8486_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8486_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents does not mention that Fernando Pessoa was influenced by Antonio Tabucchi. Instead, it states that Antonio Tabucchi was heavily influenced by the works of Fernando Pessoa."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context provided clearly indicates that Antonio Tabucchi was heavily influenced by Fernando Pessoa, not the other way around. Therefore, the statement \"Fernando Pessoa was influenced by Antonio Tabucchi\" is incorrect based on the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several pieces of text state that Tabucchi was heavily influenced by Pessoa, specifically mentioning his use of heteronyms and exploration of complex identities. The provided information does not suggest a reverse influence from Tabucchi to Pessoa.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It is explicitly stated that Antonio Tabucchi was heavily influenced by Fernando Pessoa, especially his use of heteronyms and exploration of complex identities. This suggests a flow of influence from Pessoa to Tabucchi, not the other way around.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Antonio Tabucchi was heavily influenced by Fernando Pessoa, as evidenced by his use of heteronyms and exploration of complex identities in his works.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}